[♪ Marvel Studios fanfare
playing]
[wind howling]
[sighs]
[Yelena] There is something
Wrong with me.
An emptiness.
I thought it started
when my sister died,
but now it feels
like something bigger.
Just a... void.
Or maybe I'm just bored.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Boo.
[both grunting]
[Yelena groans]
They send me a job,
I clock in, clock out,
you know?
[guards shouting]
[gun fires]
I'm in the cleanup business.
This week, Malaysia.
Next week, who knows?
I thought throwing myself
Info work was the answer.
But I'm not focused,
and I'm not happy,
and I don't have purpose.
And without purpose, I'm just
drifting like a river...
[gun fires]
...or like an old leaf.
Or like an old leaf
in a river.
Which do you think is bet--
'Ey!
You weren't listening to me.
It's like your mind
is somewhere else.
[whimpers]
Well, whatever.
You're useless to me unless
you can get me past that
facial recognition thingy.
[sighs]
[guard exclaims]
[gasps]
Hello.
Can you help me get in there?
No?
Mmm.
You've got your own problems,
I guess.
Well, it didn't say how
to destroy the evidence
in the assignment.
It's gonna get messy.
[lab tech] Stop right there!
Hi.
Now, that's a face
that can open a scanner.
Did Valentina send you?
This research is property
of OXE Group.
You're gonna tell me
- I don't understand.
- You don't understand.
- We've made a breakthrough.
- You've made a breakthrough.
- It's gonna change the world.
- No, no, no.
- It could end the world.
- Blah, blah, blah.
Valentina doesn't
understand what happened here.
Shh, shh, shh.
Look, blame the US government
for their pesky investigation.
Now we have to get rid
of all this stuff.
Do you think
I like taking orders?
Going from job to job doing
the same thing all the time?
Don't do it.
I wouldn't do that.
Always a struggle for a gun.
[lab tech] Oh, God.
[gunshots]
You shoot, I dodge.
[lab tech] Oh, my God.
Tell Valentina
she's making a mistake.
- [grunts]
- [gunshots]
[lab tech exclaims]
You guys can never
aim for shit.
Always collateral damage.
[both grunting]
You try to say
your last words.
Project Sentry isn't
what she thinks.
But you start to fall asleep.
[yelps]
[gunshot]
Oh...
[sighs]
Oh, damn.
I needed that face.
Okay.
The assignment is--
Oh, wait. Hang on.
[crowd screams]
Assignment is complete.
What's next?
[reporter]
Representative Barnes,
as a freshman congressman,
any words on today's hearing?
Well, I'm not
on the impeachment committee,
but the rumors of wrongdoing
are, um, very worrying.
They are, uh, very,
very concerning and worrying.
And, uh, I think that
my Brooklyn constituents
deserve better,
so we're-we're gonna get
to the bottom of this,
um... [clears throat]
...worrying issue.
Thank you.
[reporters clamoring]
[gavel banging]
[congressman] Now, today,
the committee is meeting
to examine this official
who sits before you.
Articles of impeachment
have been brought against her.
And when we vote
in favor of the impeachment,
she will be removed
from her post permanently.
Please state your name
for the record.
Valentina Allegra de Fontaine.
Mm-hmm.
- Uh, Miss Fontaine--
- [Valentina] No.
It's "de Fontaine."
You forgot the "de.”
Mr. Anderson, for example,
is Secretary of Defense,
not secretary of "fense.”
[attendees chuckle]
[congressman]
Miss de Fontaine.
At this moment,
you are serving
as a director of the CIA,
correct?
That is correct.
And before that, you were
the chairwoman of the board
of OXE Group?
Yes. Although, I have fully
divested in OXE
since taking office.
I now sit on the board in
a strategic guidance capacity.
And following
this strategic guidance,
the OXE Group
maintains significant holdings
in unregulated labs
in foreign countries
and rumored
human experimentation.
All part
of an illegal operation
to develop your own
super... person.
May I speak now, Congressman?
Yes.
First of all,
I don't have time
to entertain these rumors
and this gossip.
Right now, there are
multiple rogue nations
with technologies
that far exceed our own.
And you'll recall that
our last president turned into
a bright red
superhuman monster
who nearly
destroyed this city.
The Avengers are not
walking through that door.
We have no reliable heroes.
That is why
the onus is on me, on us,
the American government,
to shield its citizens.
- And you know...
- [gavel bangs]
Madame Director.
...anything I have done
in my roles,
both at OXE or at the CIA,
has been done
with that goal in mind.
- [gavel bangs]
- Order. Madame Director.
I officially reject
these articles of impeachment.
This is a partisan
waste of time.
And your hunt
will come up empty,
no matter how many
nooks and crannies
you happen
to stick your nose in.
So you don't mind
if this committee continues
this investigation?
Oh, of course not.
Shit.
We gotta get all of this
outta here ASAP.
Yep. So far they've removed
all the case studies...
Okay, just get rid
of any hanging chads
that could get me impeached
or land me in federal prison.
Copy. No prison.
[Valentina] What about our shadow ops
out in the field?
Did all those loose ends
get tied up?
Well, the ends are tied, yes,
but the rope is on fire.
What?
Can you please
just say it normal?
Okay, um, one operative
blew up an entire laboratory
in the middle of Kuala Lumpur.
Whatever.
Did the new assignments
get sent out?
Yes, ma'am.
All but one have checked in.
Where is she?
[viewer laughing, chewing]
There's Brezhnev.
Those guys
with the little waves.
Get out of my way.
- Get out of my--
- [doorbell rings]
I click "leave on porch."”
[doorbell rings]
Your "subordinance" will
be reported to DoorDash HQ.
[Yelena]
Alexei, it's me. Open up.
Yelena?
Hold on!
[sighs]
"Protecting you
from boring evening."
- Hmm.
- [door opens]
Yelena! So good to see you.
Hi, Dad.
Sorry for the wait.
I was on important call.
Highly classified.
How long has it been, huh?
A year?
Wow, yeah, I guess--
I guess it has been.
You-- You've been busy
with work?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, a lot of, uh...
a lot of work.
- Me too.
- Too many irons in fire.
Uh, security.
My limo business.
You would not believe
the important people
I meet driving. [chuckles]
So you... you feel fulfilled?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so full, so filled.
Move to DC,
best decision I ever made.
Isn't this technically
Baltimore?
No. Baltimore start
next block over.
- Oh.
- But why do you ask this?
What, uh--
What brings you here?
Uh, |-- I wanted to talk
to you about Valentina.
[chuckling] Okay.
New assignment.
You come to Red Guardian.
You want a little help.
Uh, no, I--
I think I'm gonna quit.
What?
I would burn the city
to the ground to work for her.
What? You just said
you were fulfilled.
Lena, I was lying.
Look around you.
I'm miserable.
Give me her number.
- No way.
- Give to me.
- Alexei, stop, stop.
- I call her. I use--
Lena!
Lena, what is wrong?
The light inside you is dim
even by
Eastern European standards.
I've just been wondering,
you know,
like, what... is the point?
In any of this?
The point of work
is fame and fortune.
Fortune buys friends,
and love,
and a lot of cool clothes.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay, okay--
- No, never mind. It's fine.
- No, no, no. Okay.
You-You want to know
when I was really happy?
Yes, please.
When I was serving my country
as a hero.
Saving civilians in streets.
Being cheered on by the crowd.
Adored like a god.
[speaking Russian]
There is no higher calling.
Your sister understood
something about that.
Mm-mmm.
Perhaps it is time
that you followed in her path.
Why do you have
this photo out?
We were so bad.
You were happy.
I'll make you something.
You know, I'm still
super soldier in his prime.
Maybe you could
put in a good word
with Valentina for me, huh?
Okay, Val. Reporting for duty.
What's my next assignment?
Thank you, Ms. Belova.
I was starting to worry.
After this though,
I-- I need a change.
[Valentina] Oh, really?
Yeah, maybe something
more public facing.
Interesting.
Yelena's ready
for her close-up?
[chuckles]
Yeah, this just
isn't working for me anymore.
[Valentina sighs] Okay, well,
you know I love
promoting women.
You complete this
last assignment for OXE,
and you have a deal.
Okay?
Okay.
[Valentina]
There's a warehouse facility,
a vault, built a mile down
into a mountain.
It stores all of OXE Group's
most sensitive assets.
Intel's come in
that a rogue operative
with attributes
perfectly tailored to rob me
is intending to...
well, rob me.
I need you
to follow the target inside
and find out
what she intends to steal.
I'll add your biometrics
to the system.
You'll have full access.
- [alarm blares]
- [door hisses]
Once you assess
what's being stolen,
you have the go-ahead
to terminate on sight.
And then, no problem.
You know, we can find you
some "good guy” material.
It's simple, really.
It's just one little target...
and you're done.
[both grunting]
What is happening?
You're not even my target.
You're mine.
I'm not here for you.
[sighs] There you are.
Now what?
[Ava] Oh, get over yourself.
[Yelena shouts]
[Ava] Stay out of my way.
[Walker groans]
[both straining]
[gun fires]
[stranger retching]
[stranger groaning]
Is she actually dead? Oh...
Whoa. No. Hi. Hey. [chuckles]
[stammering] I'm-- I'm Bob.
[♪ jazz music playing]
[Valentina] Yes, these are
the Chitauri handcuffs.
Recovered from
the Battle of New York
by the first responders.
They came
with the new property.
Just reminds us that,
of course, we struggle,
but then we get back up.
- Yes, we do.
- I love it. Yeah.
- That's inspiring.
- Oh. [chuckles]
Thank you, Congressman.
I'm so happy that you're here.
Yes, this is
a beautiful fake event, Val.
"The First Responders
Family Fund."
- Yes.
- That's cute.
Cute? Oh.
This won't sway the votes
enough to save your ass.
Oh. [chuckles]
Okay. So, can you go
get him, Mel?
- Yep.
- Thank you.
This gaudy Avenger propaganda
reeks of desperation.
If you really thought that,
you wouldn't be here.
You're scared
because your investigation
of my office came up clean.
- Hmm. Squeaky clean.
- Mm-hmm.
Almost like someone
had frantically gotten rid
of all the evidence.
Or like someone
was incredibly innocent.
Without proof,
this impeachment thing
IS running on borrowed time.
[photographer] Uh, excuse me.
Turn around.
Oh. [laughs]
- How great.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you very much.
Ah...
What do you think?
Oh.
- Hi.
- Mel, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mmm.
This must all seem like
ancient history to you.
You know, Kierkegaard says
that life can only
be understood backwards.
- Very true.
- Is it?
I don't know, actually.
It did sound good, though.
He did believe that
it was up to individuals
- to create values.
- Hmm.
I know who you are
and what you're doing.
What am I doing?
You're working me.
You're trying to get me
on your side.
Okay, look. I...
Y-You say you know who I am.
So you know my story,
and you know I didn't have
a choice who I worked for.
But you do.
I need to keep Valentina
on schedule.
[sighs] Oh.
What is this? This your trash?
- It's my business card.
- Oh.
In case you need some help or,
you know, you wanna share
some secret hidden evidence.
Ah.
Okay. Goodbye.
Who are you?
I'm-- I'm Bob. I told you.
I'm, uh...
Yeah. [chuckles] Bob.
Jesus Christ.
Stop saying "Bob."
- Who sent you, Bob?
- [Bob] Nobody.
Why would I be sent?
Were you all--
You were all sent?
[Ava] Okay, I'm not sure
what's happening here,
but you're all exhausting
and my job is done, so--
Ah, but you see my job
is to keep an eye on you.
So, no, you are not gonna go
anywhere anymore.
So you're keeping
an eye on her, huh?
That's a halfway decent cover
for somebody stealing assets
from OXE.
I'm not stealing.
She's stealing.
[sighs]
Okay.
It's clear we have all
worked for Valentina
in some sort of
shadow ops capacity.
Yeah. So?
So all of this stuff
is OXE's secrets.
But so are we.
Which makes us liabilities
that no one would miss.
Oh, speak for yourself.
We are the evidence,
and this is the shredder.
She wants us gone.
Your theory's flawed.
Oh, please. Go on.
Okay. Well, look at the facts.
The infamous Ghost.
A SHIELD reject on the run
from 15 nations?
'Cause the dead one
over there,
she destroyed
half of Budapest.
Don't talk about her
like that.
And you,
former Red Room assassin.
God only knows
the blood on your hands.
Pretty ludicrous
coming from the dime-store
Captain America.
I'll have you know
I was actually
the official Captain America,
SO...
[scoffs]
Yeah, for, like, two seconds.
Before you publicly murdered
an innocent man
on the streets.
- Do I have that right?
- Really? Define "innocent.”
Hey, look. I'm a decorated
combat veteran, okay?
I have a loving wife
and a son.
Let's be honest, you guys are
just cheap mercenaries. Okay?
So, I-- Clearly, I'm supposed
to bring you in.
[both laughing]
That was funny.
Thank you. We needed that.
[Bob laughs]
It was getting so tense
in here for a second.
[clears throat]
I'm not leaving here
without completing my mission.
Valentina gave me
a clean slate guarantee,
and I'm not screwing that up.
But this weirdo wasn't part
of the job, so I gotta know...
How'd you get in?
[sighs]
I don't-- I don't remember.
Terrific answer.
All right, um...
Tie yourselves up.
- Wow. No.
- Oh, my God.
And goodbye.
- [high-pitched buzzing]
- [exclaims]
[buzzing stops]
[pants]
[groans]
You guys hear that?
Isn't that amazing? Cheers.
And she said,
"Not on my watch."
[♪ jazz music playing]
- Congressman Gary.
- Hey!
I have a plan.
Holy shit, Bucky.
The assistant, she's ductile.
- Ductile? Oh.
- Yeah.
I-I mean, good.
But next time,
why don't you just text me
like a normal person?
Look, we're safe here.
We're in a blind spot, okay?
Away from those two cameras.
Just hold on, all right?
We don't need to go rogue
in the darkness,
or whatever you people do.
Hold on”? You don't know
what Val is capable of.
We need to move fast,
and the assistant
is on the fence.
Without a smoking gun,
the best chance to get Val out
of power is to whip the votes.
And you can help with that
and then let the system
do its job.
The system that goes on recess
every day at 4:00 p.m.
We are in a good spot,
I assure you.
My team is putting together
a juicy packet
for the next hearing.
- Packet?
- Yes, Bucky.
Read the packets.
Is it time?
I can confirm all your
"guests" are in attendance,
and vault level five has been
completely sealed off.
All right, then.
"All right, then. Move on
to the final step"? Or...
Torch it all.
Right. Um...
- Are you-- Are you sure?
- Oh, my God.
[Yelena] Hey.
Job or not, can you have
some respect, please?
Yeah, Jesus.
Hold on a second.
What? She'd want me
to have it. [chuckles]
I need it.
[alarm blaring]
[mechanical hissing, whirring]
What the hell is that?
That doesn't sound
like a shredder.
It's an incinerator.
Two minutes.
Then Valentina's slate
Is wiped clean.
You don't know that for sure.
Could be for anything.
Could be for when they come
to pick me up.
[Ava] Do you feel that?
The temperature rising
dramatically
as if heat was involved?
Okay, it's an incinerator.
Oh, boy. That is no way to go.
Well, how would you
like to die today, Bob?
Okay, ghost lady.
- Ava.
- Sure. Whatever. Don't care.
We need to get you
through the walls,
so that you can open the door.
- She tried that already.
- I know she did.
But we haven't tried shutting
down the sound barrier.
Well, if they built it
just for her,
there's gotta be
an independent power source.
[Ava] Come on. Let's go.
What-- What exactly
are we looking for?
We're looking for
not-stupid questions, Bob.
[Yelena] I think I found it.
Move!
I can override this.
On your left!
Or that works, I hope.
Go, go, go.
You think she's coming back?
I should have
seen this coming.
- [alarm blares]
- [door hisses]
[child] Yelena!
Yelena!
[in Russian] Yelena, c'mon!
What?
[in Russian]
Lunch will be over soon.
Why'd you bring us so far out?
[in Russian] Anya, over here!
No.
[in Russian] I'm sorry.
[in Russian] Well done, Yelena.
Your first test is
now complete.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey. Didn't think
you'd come back. Thanks.
[sighs] I had to. Someone cut
the power to the elevator.
[Mel] Lovely evening.
Nice to be in the room,
you know?
Okay. What is it, Mel?
Just spit it out already.
What?
Um, it's your "guests."
They've somehow evaded
the "housewarming gift."
- Oh, come on.
- And, um...
God, is it possible
that they've maybe, um,
joined forces against you?
[scoffs]
Mel.
These are defective losers.
Antisocial tragedy
in human form.
You know, honestly,
I cannot think
of a worse group of people
trying to work together.
- My god. [chuckles]
- Right.
It's just that, um...
- What?
- They're working together.
[Valentina] What--
Who the hell is this guy?
I have no idea.
I need an ID on John Doe.
I wanna know how this man-boy
got into my supposedly
impenetrable stronghold.
- Copy.
- And call Holt.
Give him
the vault coordinates.
I want the full strike team
mobilized.
- We need to end this now.
- Okay.
Calling now.
Holt? It's Mel.
Ready for coordinates?
40... [continues indistinctly]
I was trying to help...
Everybody's got a reason for
being here except this guy.
- Hey, Bobby.
- [helmet drops]
Less talking to yourself,
more talking to us.
[muttering]
- I'm tired of this bullshit.
- Hey, Walker.
You tell me how you got
in here right goddamn now.
I swear, man, |-I just woke up
in this place.
One minute, I was, you know,
getting my blood drawn
for this medical study,
and the next I'm in here.
[chuckles] In my pajamas.
I don't know what's happening.
Okay, then show me
where you woke up.
In-- In there.
Where everything's on fire.
That's real convenient.
Walker, relax.
You don't remember anything?
Bag over your head?
- A needle in your neck?
- No.
- Choke hold? Nerve pinch?
I think he's just a civilian.
If he's a civilian,
he knows too much.
If he's an agent, he sucks.
Either way I say we
throw him back into the fire.
[chuckling]
Sorry. Look-- You said
you were Captain America?
Why are you laughing?
Just 'cause you're an asshole.
You know?
[chuckles]
It's just funny. I mean...
[Yelena] Hey. Whoa.
Okay. Okay!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We swung our tiny dicks.
It was a lot of fun.
You go over there.
Bob, come with me.
Come here.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
You do not seem fine.
[chuckles]
Yeah, well, we've only
just met. This is...
This is how I am.
Oh.
The talking to yourself?
Yeah.
- The emo aggressive thing?
- I mean--
That-- That guy's been
a dick to me from the start.
Oh, I get it. He sucks.
But we have to work together
to get out of here, so...
Well, you guys should just go
without me. It'll be easier.
Oh, no, you'll die down here.
[scoffs]
Yeah. Well, whatever.
I mean...
I think everyone's better off
if I just stay put.
Okay, I-I-- I understand.
We all feel like shit
sometimes.
And loneliness, I get that.
I get it.
And that--
that darkness gets...
[chuckling]
...pretty enticing.
And then it starts to feel
a little bit like a...
[sighs]
A void.
Yep. A void.
What do you do about it?
You shove it way down.
You just...
- push it down.
- [chuckles]
[both laugh]
That's great--
That's really good advice.
[scoffs] You're welcome.
[crash]
[Walker grunts]
You guys done
with therapy yet?
I think I found a way out.
Look, we're all alone.
All of us.
Let's just stick together
until we make it
to the surface,
and after that,
you can start a fight
with a super soldier.
Get yourself killed.
I don't care.
Okay?
Okay. Yeah.
"If the resolution
of impeachment is adopted...”
Stupid packets.
Oh, God. Boring.
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
Hi. This is, uh, Mel.
Mel. Hi.
- You called.
- I did.
I know that you're new to DC,
and I wanted to, um, network.
- Network?
- Mm-hmm.
[machine beeps]
So, uh, how are you feeling
about your new job?
Oh, it's great. Love it.
It's not ancient history,
you know.
I was in high school
when the aliens came.
And the Avengers.
High school, huh?
I was, like, 90.
[Mel laughs]
It's kinda strange
that it's all over now, right?
I mean, Avengers are gone.
No one else is coming
to save the day.
Maybe we could be
the people that are coming.
Just come in
and testify against her.
[Mel scoffs]
You must really
not know my boss.
We can protect you.
Oh, can you?
Is that coming from
the freshman congressman
who hasn't gotten
a bill passed
or the Winter Soldier?
Come on, Mel.
Just give me something.
[door opens]
[whispering] Hey--
You can track my phone, right?
Yes, I can,
but I don't do that anymore.
Thank you, Congressman.
Have a great night.
[Yelena grunts]
[Yelena] So,
none of us fly?
What, do we all just
punch and shoot?
Okay. Don't worry. I got this.
[grunts]
[grunts, groans]
You should try that again.
[groans]
We're pretty far down here.
[Yelena laughs]
Hey. Okay, why don't you
walk up
through the walls or whatever
and then just
throw us a rope down?
- Yeah.
- That's...
Okay, well, first of all,
someone other than you
would have to ask me.
And second of all, I'd have
to know where I'm going
'cause I've never been able to
hold it longer than a minute.
So I'd just get lost
in an ocean of dirt,
and then I'd be
crushed to death.
- All right?
- Just a minute?
- Oh, shut up.
- Oh, my God. We suck.
Uh...
I have an idea.
[all grunting]
Right.
Left.
[Walker] Right.
Ew. Which one of you is wet?
I-- I run hot. Sorry.
Someone's got
a weird, hard butt.
That's not my butt.
It's my suit.
[Yelena] Well, you need to
get a new suit.
[Ava] Pardon me
for the inconvenience.
I mean, I only spent
my entire life in labs
hooked up to machines
so I could create
this physical cage
to keep my material body from
disintegrating at all times.
So, yeah, I'm so sorry
about that.
[laughs]
You do not want to start
the whole sob story game.
I win.
Enslaved child assassin
over here.
Well, you were just
a kid, so...
Oh, so that's
a good thing now?
I just think it might be nice
to know that you didn't
really know any better.
Thanks. I feel way better.
Hey, quit it.
[all panting]
Uh...
All right.
- Okay. Okay.
- Ready?
[Walker straining]
Right. Oh, God.
[Mel gasps]
[Valentina] Oh, my God.
Why are you gasping?
Please don't gasp at work.
It's the John Doe.
He's Sentry Project.
No, everyone who went through
Sentry Project is dead, Mel.
That's why we're in
this whole stupid mess.
Yeah, but look. There.
Robert Reynolds entered the
pre-trial program in Malaysia,
and he'd had a real rough go
before that.
One of the test subjects.
How did he get in my vault?
He was supposed to be dead.
You threw him out
with the rest of the evidence.
If he survived the procedure,
that means...
Yeah. It might actually work.
Oh, my God.
[all grunting]
[Ava] It's crazy.
I can't even see the floor.
Can we not talk about
how high up we are?
I'm just not great
with heights.
Hey, I think I see the door.
- [Walker] Yeah. Yeah.
- [Yelena] Okay. Okay.
Uh...
Now what?
Um...
I guess one of us should go...
first.
Then the other three
immediately fall.
Shit.
[Bob] Sorry.
Yeah, I guess I didn't...
I didn't really
think this far ahead.
[Walker] Genius plan, Bobby.
- Always making things worse.
- [groans] These bloody boots.
I don't think
I can hold this much longer.
Okay. Hand me your baton.
- I can reach it.
- What?
- [Walker] Yeah.
- No way.
You're just going to leave us.
Okay.
- Spin us around...
- [sniffling]
...and then I can...
I can latch us on.
I'm not spinning us around,
okay?
Somebody's got to go first.
Cucumber, cucumber, cucumber.
What the hell is happening?
Growing up, somebody told me
that you can stop a sneeze
if you confuse your brain.
I always just yelled
"cucumber.”
- Okay.
- I have to sneeze.
But if I sneeze, then
I'm going to lose control.
This is insane, okay?
I can get us all out of here.
- I just need to go first.
- No.
There's got to be another way.
[exhales] Oh, no.
- Cucumber! Cucumber!
All right! Come on! Okay,
just give me this. I got it!
[all shouting]
[grunts]
[grunts, pants]
[sneezes]
You selfish prick.
Yet, you're all safe.
I made a tactical decision
to secure my own safety
and ensure all yours.
Pretty ungrateful
if you ask me, but...
You gonna make it, Bobby?
Looks like you might have
missed arm, leg and chest day.
[baby fusses]
- [Olivia] John?
- What?
[Olivia] Are you watching him?
What? I'm doing it.
I'm watching him.
[baby cries]
- John.
- What, Olivia? What?
- Please.
- I'm watching him. He's fine.
You're in your phone.
Look, you don't like
the way that I do it,
then you can do it yourself,
okay?
[baby crying]
It's okay. It's okay.
[Yelena] Walker.
Uh...
What the hell are you doing?
I'm fine.
[Ava] All right,
let's get out of here.
[people clamoring]
[Yelena] Okay, we need
to come up with a plan.
- [Walker] Here's what we're gonna do.
- You're the boss now? Cute.
Yeah, it's our only chance
of getting out of here, so...
Okay, I think I might
just surrender, probably.
Okay, fine.
Every man for himself.
Why should you be in charge?
You almost killed all of us
right there.
Well, let's see.
I've been in the trenches
of every war-torn country
on this planet,
rescued God knows
how many hostages
and shook the hands
of two US presidents.
What else? Uh...
Oh, high school state football
champs back-to-back-to-back.
- Go Bears.
- Oh, wow.
When I was five,
I was in a peewee soccer team
called the West Chesapeake
Valley Thunderbolts
sponsored by
Shane's Tire Shop.
We won zero games,
and one time,
this girl, Mindy,
she did a poo at midfield.
Anyone else have any pointless
childhood stories to tell?
Grew up in a lab prison.
Meth-addicted
sign-twirling chicken.
It was a summer job.
Right. Okay, here's the plan.
We set off an explosion
to bring them in.
No. Too many variables
with an explosion.
They turn on
their night vision.
You handle the first wave,
but you wait for me
after I've blinded
the remaining troops.
- I'm just going to wait for ya?
- It will only work if you wait.
[Walker] Terrible plan.
- Ava, you...
- [Ava's suit activates]
...find an escape vehicle.
Uh, what about me?
You stay behind me, Bob.
[sighs]
Let's do this.
[Valentina] What's the latest?
We're dug in, ma'am.
Got it covered
from all angles.
There's no way out.
Breach team ready
at the front.
It's going to be
non-lethal protocol.
Non-lethal? No one told me
this was non-lethal.
Well, I'm telling you now,
Holt.
It's just...
I've spent a lot of time
planning for lethal.
Then change the plan. Okay?
There's somebody inside there
I don't want
catching any strays.
[agent] Get down!
Strike Team 4, enter now.
Non-lethal.
In one minute,
these all go back on.
Okay.
Maybe I should have a gun?
Hmm. No, I don't think so.
But we are gonna need--
We're gonna need
to fight, right? So...
Mm-hmm. I will fight.
You stay behind me.
The medical trial was supposed
to make me better,
and, I don't know, I feel like
maybe I could help.
I thought you said that you
didn't know anything about it.
No, not much. I just remember
they said it was for people
who wanted to make something
better of themselves.
Mmm.
You can trust me, Bob.
Can I?
No, not really.
[both chuckle]
I-- I've always had these
episodes since I was a kid.
There's a... There's a high,
then there's a big low,
and then my memory
just goes blank.
But this time,
I feel like there's...
I don't know,
something bad happened
or I did something bad.
I mean, everyone here
has done bad things.
I think this was like
a whole new kind of--
- [device beeps]
- Oh.
Lights up.
No. Why...
Why did that not work?
Well, you got to turn
the power back on.
I mean, you got to blind
the guys.
- Yeah, I know that, Bob.
- That was your plan.
You're not being helpful, Bob.
Give me that. Follow me.
I hate to say it, but I think
Walter was right on this one.
His name is Walker, Bob.
Turn on the lights, Yelena.
[breathing heavily]
I got to do everything myself.
[grunts]
[gunshots]
[shushes]
I will repeat,
Tango Foxtrot Lima
requesting report.
Next team up, get in there!
- Where is he?
- He's gone.
Every man for himself, right?
- [Yelena] Shit.
- [Bob] Oh.
[grunting]
[Yelena] Get down!
- [Bob] I can help.
- Stay behind me.
[groans]
Bob, stay!
That's it. You're done.
No, wait! I can help!
- Take this!
- Yes! How-- How do I use it?
You point and shoot.
Shit.
- Sorry!
- A little higher!
- That was awesome.
- Not at me!
No! Stop! Stop shooting!
Stop! Stop! It's me!
It's John! Stop!
- Where were you?
The explosion fried the wires.
I told you, too many variables.
I knew it.
- And then, you didn't wait.
- I did wait! And the--
[Holt on radio]
What's going on in there?
Do we need to go lethal?
- [radio beeps]
- Okay.
We probably got
about 60 seconds
until they mobilize.
And if ghost lady actually did
what she was supposed to,
maybe we'll all
get out of here alive.
[Bob] I don't really want
to be carried anymore.
[Walker] Shut up, Bob.
You're injured, remember?
[Walker] We need a truck.
[Yelena] Where's Ava?
[Walker] She's gone.
Of course she's gone.
[Bob] Now what?
Hey! Get in.
[Yelena] You going
to be okay back here?
- Yeah. All good.
- Yeah? Okay.
Second time you came back.
[chuckles]
This was the only
way out, okay?
- That's all.
- All right.
[Walker] Oh, shit.
All right. Just, uh,
let me do the talking, okay?
- [Yelena] Oh, my God.
- Here we go.
Identify yourself, soldiers.
Part of the medical team.
Need to get the wounded
to the hospital.
[agent] Medical bay's set up
north side.
[Walker] Nah,
medical bay won't suffice.
We were headed off-base.
[agent]
No one leaves the premises
until mission is completed.
Orders are no deviations
from protocol.
Identify yourself.
- No.
- Oh, wow, masterful.
Remove your helmets
and identify yourself.
Now, soldiers!
You are messing
with the wrong--
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
[Bob] Hey!
Over here!
Move, move, move!
Oh, no. Bob helped.
Open fire. End this now.
I want him toes up.
[guns fire]
What the hell are you doing?
This has gone far--
[yelps, chokes]
Cease fire! Cease fire!
[agent] Cease fire!
[Ava] Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
That's why he did it.
[agent] What the...
[guns fire]
Is that...
Mel, I need you to connect me
to our satellites.
I need to know exactly where
he's going, and I need it now.
I, uh... I think he's coming
back down.
- No. No, no, no.
- Oh, shit.
[Ava grunts]
[Walker] Oh, God.
[Yelena] I'll call an Uber.
Jesus Christ.
I know. What was that?
That was her.
She did that to him.
Well, she turned him into
a tomahawk cruise missile.
You were right,
she definitely wants us dead.
To test on someone like that,
it's inhuman.
Yeah, she's lost it.
Nope. She's found it.
And she'll use it.
What is this?
"Power of a thousand
exploding suns."
"Golden Guardian of Good."
That's a mouthful.
Wow.
Sentry.
Very shiny,
I'll give them that.
[Ava] And what do you know
about this?
There was a rumor
that OXE was on the verge
of some kind
of big breakthrough.
Whatever it was
was way too extreme.
Test subjects were dying.
When the government looked
into it,
Val shut it down.
She put me on cleanup duty.
Let's just make it home
without getting cratered.
Might need new homes.
Anybody hungry?
Cactus berry.
Let me see here.
So, um, that woman
back there that |I...
You knew her?
Yeah, I did.
She had a tough life.
She killed a lot of people,
and then she got killed.
Same as us someday.
It's a shit life.
Yeah, well...
what other life can we have?
[Ava] Says the guy with
the Norman Rockwell family
waiting for him at home.
Yeah.
How do you do it?
Well, you just keep working
at it every day.
Never give up.
Beautiful.
Dr. Phil,
that was really beautiful.
Yeah. You know that show's
not on anymore, right?
[Yelena]
Yeah, it is. I watch it.
[Walker] Nah, it got canceled
a few years ago.
It was a good show
while it was on,
but it's not on anymore.
Gotta be like a YouTube thing.
They took him off cable.
[Mel] Well, it isn't great.
Seven local outlets
have picked up
the story of the blast.
One has already connected
the vault to OXE.
And I have 15 messages
from concerned House members
on our side of the aisle.
[Valentina] You know,
I don't say it enough,
but I am so impressed
that in circumstances
like this,
you can still get me
a good cup of coffee.
It's extraordinary.
[Mel] Thank you.
[Valentina]
Okay, time to pivot.
I'm gonna need
a new team of scientists.
And I want them there
when we arrive.
Okay. DC?
Mm-mmm. No. The new place.
Oh. But, uh, we stopped
mid-renovation.
When we shut down the project.
Exactly.
We're officially unshut down.
What about Yelena
and the others?
Nothing yet.
Get rid of them, Mel.
They're the last piece
of evidence.
On it.
Let me know when our boy
in the box gets to New York.
[Ava, Walker, Yelena panting]
[Walker] Those birds
are way too high.
They're doing recon loops
at 4,000 feet.
I mean, they don't know
what they're doing.
They'll be five or ten klicks
away in no time.
All right, Walker, we get it.
You were in the military.
Five or ten klicks
to the bird.
[exclaims]
There.
[Walker] Uh, it's a...
I don't... What is that?
[car horn beeping]
Oh, no.
What?
[Walker]
It's coming right at us.
- [Ava] Who is that?
- It's no one.
It's nothing.
[beeping continues]
[beeping stops]
- Oh, God.
- Yelena!
It's your dad!
Don't go in the vault!
Valentina's gonna
burn you alive!
Yelena!
[Alexei] So, I finagled
to pick up Miss de Fontaine
at fancy event.
I figure good networking,
but as soon as I overhear
the coordinates of the vault,
I rush home,
I get the tactical beast.
And then,
I drive straight here.
Oh, America's so big.
You ever drive
through Oklahoma?
It's so flat.
Oh, I forgot to tell you,
don't drink
from the Big Gulp back there.
[Yelena]
Alexei, have you slept?
I'll sleep when I'm dead!
Uh, I'd like not to die today.
So maybe somebody else
should be driving.
[Alexei] Mr. Walker,
second coming
of Captain America.
You and I have
lot in common, you know?
I too was state-sponsored
super soldier in Russia.
Mmm. But also very different
because Walker actually knows
what he's doing.
[Alexei] And Ghost.
Ah, what a magician.
You disappear. You reappear.
When you reappear,
does sometimes things
not pop up in right place?
Oh. I find it best
just to ignore him sometimes.
What impressive friends
you've assembled, Yelena.
We are not friends, Alexei.
Nah. We're just
disposable delinquents.
Whatever you are,
the light inside you
is brighter, Yelena.
How about this?
You are a team
of scrappy antiheroes.
- Yeah. Go Thunderbolts.
- What?
- Yelena...
- Oh, my God.
You named them
after your peewee soccer club?
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- [chuckles]
The West Chesapeake Valley
Thunderbolts.
Sponsored by
Dmitri's Elite Industrial
Lighting and Electronics.
No, no.
Never won a game,
but Yelena had so much fun.
There was a girl who pooped...
- No. It was-- It was not--
- ...In one game.
It was crazy.
I was yelling at the ref.
It was sponsored
by Shane's Tire Shop.
- Shane?
- Yes.
- What's this talk of Shane?
- It was.
He didn't have
that kind of money.
- Yes, it was.
- No! Shane? What a joke.
You really need to sleep.
Okay. What about
this Bob you mentioned?
What's the plan?
Where am I driving?
It's not like that.
We need to escape
and we need to hide.
Yeah, way smarter
for us to split up.
There's actually
an airfield not far from here.
We'll just disappear
from there.
Split up? No, no, no.
You may not see what I see,
but I have been around
long time.
No shit.
This has the makings of a team
that can raise to glory.
A team that can bring light
from the darkness.
A team of heroes that can be
on the Wheaties box
- and have little kiddie toy...
- No, no.
This is not
a marketing opportunity, okay?
Valentina is hunting us,
and we cannot win.
Do you understand?
- You don't understand.
- I do. You don't.
Look, you say that Valentina
is going to use the power
- of this Sentry Project...
- Yes.
...to take over
and kill us all.
Then you need to
stand up to her.
You and your team.
You got a convoy
approaching fast.
- Step on it.
- Aye, aye, Captain.
[Ava] Is that it?
- Okay, any time now.
- Yeah. We're working on it.
- [Yelena] A little bit faster.
- [Alexei] Takes a second.
[Yelena] Alexei!
- Alexei!
- Okay! Don't worry!
Don't worry.
She's bulletproof, huh?
Engaging defensive measures.
[♪ sensual R&B music playing,
Ginuwine "Pony"]
What the hell? [groaning]
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit. Wait, that's not
supposed to do that.
- [Yelena] Oh, my God.
- Come on.
Who are you driving?
Walker, shield!
What happened
to "bulletproof"?
- Bulletproof-ish.
- Jesus Christ!
God,
everyone's a critic today!
Time to break out
the bottle service.
Come on, Ghost,
give me the good stuff.
Okay, not really appropriate.
Vodka! Vodka, now!
Oh, my God.
This is so not the time.
[groans]
What's wrong with you?
[laughs]
No, no, no!
Give me a break.
[sighs]
Okay, I'll be back. I hope.
[high-pitched tone blares]
[grunts, groans]
[Alexei] Yelena!
What are you doing?
There's nothing you can do.
[Alexei] What?
[device beeping]
It's Bucky!
[chuckles] The Winter Soldier.
[engine revs]
[chuckles]
That's what I talk about!
- Yes! Yeah!
- Woo!
[cheering]
Oh, sh--
[reporter] Congressman!
Why did you call
an emergency session
of the impeachment committee?
What I can say
is that I've gotten
a tip from a trusted cohort
that will be
bringing some new evidence in,
and that evidence is juicy.
The impeachment
was just an appetizer.
They should be
getting a nice, cozy cell
in federal prison
ready for Miss Fontaine.
I just got word
the impeachment committee
is convening tonight.
This is serious, Val.
Were you able to
get the lab fully operational?
[Mel] Yes,
but the rest of the building
is only 70% finished.
[Valentina] Okay.
Mel, we'll get it there.
Welcome to the Watchtower.
[Mel] Val?
Something happened
in Malaysia.
Have you read his file?
Delusions of grandeur,
depression.
Someone that imbalanced
amplified by the treatment...
The people in the labs,
they were just test subjects.
They were never gonna
be the one.
Does this
look nurturing enough?
[sighs] Very nurturing.
Hi. How--
How are you feeling, Robert?
Are you comfortable?
Yeah.
My name is
Valentina Allegra de Fontaine.
Oh, no, no, no.
You-- You tried to kill us,
- didn't you?
- [shushes]
Let me explain.
Would-- Would you like that?
Yeah.
You signed up
for a medical study which was,
as advertised,
at the cutting edge
of human improvement.
But not everybody could handle
the amount of greatness
that we had in mind.
What happened to Yelena?
Yelena? Oh.
Well, those people
you were with,
those are not honest people.
They're criminals.
Villains, really.
No, no. They-- They helped me.
[Valentina scoffs]
Robert.
Let's just forget about them,
and let's focus on you.
And how perfect you are.
Perfect, huh?
You always thought of yourself
as a victim.
But you overcame.
You went to Malaysia.
You were lost, right?
You were searching.
And you found me.
How--
How do you know all that?
I know all of it.
I know about
your mom's mental illness.
I know about your addiction
and your juvenile record.
I mean, I even know
about the times your father--
Stop! No, no, no.
I didn't say
you could know that.
[Valentina] Robert,
I know everything about you.
And I still want you
to be my guy.
And isn't that what you want?
To be accepted? To be chosen?
No one else sees it,
but I do.
And I think maybe your past
is what makes you so perfect.
[in Italian]
Stay quiet, Valentina.
Completely quiet,
no matter what you hear.
You promise me?
[Young Valentina]
Did I do something wrong?
The man in town
asked where we live.
He said he was your friend,
so I told him.
Yes, well he was.
Remember I told you
not to talk to anyone?
Yes, daddy. I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Just stay hidden for me.
[banging on door]
You know...
I've been in this business
a long time.
There's always someone
like you, smart, but cocky.
A hungry dog who already had
a bone in his mouth.
[Valentina's dad]
Let's have a drink, shall we?
[man] You still think
you're getting away with this.
Don't worry, I'll look out
for your sweet Valentina.
[gunshot]
Would you excuse me
just for a moment?
No. All right.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I can control it.
Great.
[Valentina] All right.
Let's get the press here
in the morning.
It's time to show everyone
what I've been working on.
Val, you put a serum into
someone like Steve Rogers,
he becomes Captain America,
but you do it
to someone this unstable,
I mean, who knows
what it did to him?
That's why
we build in safeguards.
Didn't we make a kill switch?
Yeah, but we threw it out
along with everything else.
Well, then remake it.
I don't really care
who this guy was.
I do know what he can become.
Get the press here
like I asked.
[Alexei] No, no, no, no!
Just when I get
my team together.
Mr. Soldier, you are making
terrible mistake.
Save it for the committee.
What committee?
You're all evidence
in the impeachment trial
against Valentina.
- [Walker laughs]
- [Ava laughs]
We don't even work
for Valentina anymore.
She tried to kill us.
We were ordered to destroy
all of her secrets,
but really, we were just sent
to kill each other
in this vault.
- But then we met Bob.
- Yeah. Bob.
[Yelena]
There was a man in the vault.
She's done something to him.
It's called Project Sentry.
Okay, he shot up into the sky.
He exploded.
And then he crashed
into this mountain,
and then he died, didn't die--
Yes, I got it.
He's very, very scary.
- So rude.
- Okay.
"Congressman Barnes."
All right, Walker.
What's that supposed to mean?
[Walker]
Means you know me, Bucky.
So cut the shit and listen to
what we're trying to tell you.
[Bucky]
Yeah, I know you, John,
and you made your choices.
I know it's been hard
since Olivia left you
and took your kid,
but still, this is on you.
[Ava] Bucky, there won't be
a committee left. Okay?
There might not
even be a government.
She has some big--
[Bucky] Threat. Yes. I got it.
Named "Bob" or "Sentry”
who flies. Right?
And you're all heroes
going after Val,
ready to save the day.
Am I supposed to believe that?
We weren't going
after her together.
We were just trying
to get home alive, actually.
[Bucky]
That's even more pathetic.
Yeah, I know. That's what
I've been telling them.
- Shut up.
- I'm not going to shut up. No.
All right.
Plane lands in six minutes.
- [Yelena] Will you be quiet?
- Yes?
Bucky, I need your help.
What is it?
Val has gone off the rails.
I mean, Project Sentry,
it's not just a failure,
it's dangerous.
Project Sentry?
[shushes]
[Mel] She has too much power
in her hands.
And this guy is a disaster
waiting to happen.
- What guy?
- [sighs] Bob.
Bob?
Bob!
[Mel] We're at
the old Avengers place.
The press are set to come
tomorrow morning.
Someone has to do something.
Shit. Okay, I-- I have to go.
But come now, please.
Bring anyone.
Everyone you can.
[line disconnects]
Bob.
- Bob.
- How many times?
I Know.
It's bad, Bucky.
[Ava] Hang on.
What are you doing?
I'm letting you go.
You're coming with me.
Why?
[shushes]
For the glory.
Well, you know Valentina.
She's got this thing
out there.
People are gonna get hurt,
and I gotta stop her.
And you are gonna help me.
Wait. Us?
Why? You got some place to be?
Bucky, you have
the wrong people.
[sighs]
Look, I've been where you are.
You can run,
but it doesn't go away.
Sooner or later
it catches up to you,
and when it does,
it's too late.
So you can either
do something about it now,
or live with it forever.
[Yelena sighs]
Stop Val and save Bob.
- Fine.
- Mmm?
Yeah.
Go on, then.
Yes!
Yeah!
What'd you think
this job was gonna be?
[chuckles]
I don't know.
I hope I've done some good.
"Good."
Good girl. Good enough.
[scoffs]
You want to be good?
Or do you want to be somebody
who changes the world?
Can't I be both?
I mean, I thought you wanted
to change the world
for the better too.
Mel, righteousness without
power is just an opinion.
Look, you're brought up
to believe
that there's a good guy
and a bad guy.
But then eventually,
you come to realize
that there's a bad guy
and a worse guy.
And nothing else.
Let me know when
you come to your senses.
[deep breathing]
[groans]
Um, I don't know. [chuckles]
Okay, yeah. We just try again.
Yeah.
Let's just focus.
Mmm.
I believe in you.
[exhales sharply]
I can do that?
You can do anything.
People think they know you.
[scoffs]
They just see you as "Bob."
They pity Bob.
I'm the only one who knows
what your true potential is,
Robert.
And it's limitless.
[chuckles]
Ready for the next lesson?
And then I have
these little, Widow...
[imitates buzzing]
...bite things.
- And in the left...
- Yeah. I-- I remember.
And then I have this 19.
Forty-five. The long barrel.
[Ava] Mmm.
- Wow. It's big.
- Yeah. Well, it's--
- It's long.
- [Ava] Mmm.
- Yeah.
- [Ava] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay, it's a little long.
- [Ava] Yeah. Big gun.
And, uh... your--
what about your hat?
Uh, the hat? The-- The helmet?
Yeah. Whatever you want
to call it.
It's, like, cool. Right?
You like it?
Do-- Do you like the hat?
Yeah, I think
the hat's pretty--
- Pretty sweet.
- Then, cool.
What kind of super serum
did you get?
I don't know. Regular. Hydra.
Hydra? Oh.
- Fancy.
- Yes.
Mine was Soviet recreation.
But it's still good, you know?
[chuckles]
- We are same. You and me.
- Well...
I mean, we are different,
but we are same.
You know, we could
be coleaders in this, huh?
[Bucky] Little different.
You get tired, I drive.
Huh? [chuckles]
I don't get tired.
No, I mean metaphorically.
I don't actually
want to drive.
[Yelena] Are we there yet?
- Almost!
[breathes deeply]
Okay. Mr. Soldier,
what is secret plan, huh?
The plan?
Yeah.
[wheels screech]
[guard] Open up on him!
- [guard] Go, go!
- [guard 2] Open up!
- [guards yelling]
- I like this plan.
[shouts]
[both grunting]
[alarm blares]
[Valentina on PA]
Jesus, you guys,
I literally just
put that drywall in.
I left the door unlocked
for you.
Come up.
[guard gasps, groans]
[grunts]
[elevator bell dings]
How crazy is it to think
of all the monumental fights
that happened exactly here
where you're standing?
Eh. I don't really care.
I mean, the place
wasn't cheap,
but it's got good optics.
[Bucky]
Well, it's over, Valentina.
This ends today.
Congressman Barnes, wow.
You know,
I never really thought
you'd have
a promising political career.
But less than half a term?
Yikes.
We're taking you in, Val.
[scoffs]
I don't think so.
[chuckling] Junior Varsity
Captain America.
[Bucky] Walker.
Oh, nice to see you, Ava.
Yelena. You look awful.
You sure you're really ready
for that public facing role
you asked me about?
Eat shit, Valentina.
Where's Bob?
Look at you.
You are all so adorable.
Just think, I send you
down there to Kill each other,
and instead, you make nice
and you form a team.
Who's this old Santa?
I'm Alexei Shostakov.
The Red Guardian.
What?
- Where's Mel?
- Mel?
Oh, Mel. Yeah.
Uh, Mel is having
a little loyalty issue.
But I'm just so grateful
that she stayed long enough
to lure you all in.
I'm not alone.
Robert?
Oh, my God.
[Bucky] That's Bob?
Yeah, he's changed a little.
It is my great honor
to introduce to you
The Sentry.
Hey, guys.
Wow. That's cool name.
[Valentina]
All-powerful. Invincible.
Stronger than all of
the Avengers rolled into one.
And soon to be known
as Earth's mightiest hero.
Have you dyed your hair?
Yeah. Well, it was...
Yeah, it was my idea.
People love a classic hero.
Okay, I'll bite.
What's the plan?
You haven't
figured it out yet, Bucky?
Geez.
Well, at least
you're kind of cute.
You're not
going to hurt people.
Oh, no.
No, I'm not gonna hurt people.
I'm gonna hurt you.
You see, the press is
on their way here now.
And they're gonna witness
the awesome power of Sentry
as he takes down this ruthless
group of rogue agents,
thus beginning a new era
in which I decide how to keep
the American people safe,
answering to no one.
I'll be unimpeachable.
That's... never gonna happen.
Sentry, your first mission is
to take out these criminals.
I don't wanna hurt you guys.
Why don't you just turn
yourselves in? [chuckles]
No, you don't
wanna do this, Bobby.
You can call me The Sentry.
Please, don't do this.
You do not need
to listen to her.
Robert, they don't think
you're good enough.
- That's not true.
- [Valentina] Remember?
You can trust me. I know you.
I don't think that you do.
Enough talking!
No one messes
with the West Chesapeake
Valley Thunderbolts!
- [Alexei shouts]
- Thunderbolts?
Hey. No, no, no! No!
Wait!
Bob, no!
[Yelena] Alexei, wait!
[screaming]
Stop, Bob.
[all groaning]
[Valentina] I'm so glad you
were able to catch a glimpse
before your, uh...
retirement. [chuckles]
Camera crews are assembling.
Finish the job, Robert.
[Sentry] Finish the job?
No.
What?
They're not a threat to me,
so why do I need to kill them?
You need to do
what I say, Robert.
Why?
"Why"?
[Alexei]
Okay. We need new plan.
[Walker] Nah, no new plans.
That thing is just
too powerful.
We just need to regroup
and think.
There's got to be a way
to stop that guy.
[Walker] Oh, my God.
We're not regrouping.
- This isn't even a team.
- Of course we're a team.
We are the Thunderbolts.
I don't know what that means.
It's her peewee
soccer team thing. It's--
We need to go somewhere
to discuss this.
- Discuss what?
- We are going to regroup.
We are going to go
back in there.
He turned my shield
into a taco.
Oh, my God! Stop.
There is no "us."
There is no "we."
Bob changed into that thing,
and there's nothing
any of you can do about it.
And what did you do exactly?
'Cause I seem to remember
you getting your arse beat
way worse than mine.
Yeah. Yeah.
I suck. I'm terrible.
We're all terrible.
Ava, you're not a hero.
You're not even a good person.
Bitch.
[scoffs] See?
Slow down. Um-nichka.
Alexei, I am not
your um-nichka.
I haven't heard from you
or seen you in a year.
[Walker] Okay, go easy on him.
- Oh, so you're nice now?
- Is it my turn?
No, you know you're
a piece of trash, Walker.
So does your family.
Jesus.
We're all losers.
And we lost. [scoffs]
Yelena!
It-- It needs to be
more of a collaboration.
The hair, for example.
Maybe-- Maybe I should have
had more of a say.
Don't let those idiots
get in your head.
The blond is great.
You sure?
'Cause, I don't know,
I thought I liked it.
Now I'm not so sure.
Enough about the hair.
Well, it's not just
about the hair.
Well, you keep talking
No, it's everything. My suit.
My name. My missions.
I mean...
why...
why would a god take orders
from anyone at all?
I think you're throwing around
the word "god"
a bit loosely there.
No, no. Because you said I was
all-powerful, invincible,
and stronger than
a whole team of Avengers,
which includes
at least one god, so...
But I'm starting to think
maybe you don't
know what I am.
Oh, goddamn it.
[Bob] Or what I'm capable of.
- [Valentina sighs]
- Maybe I need to show you.
[sighs] This is so irritating.
You were gonna turn on me,
just like the rest of them.
I'm not afraid of you, Robert.
[chuckles]
It's not Robert
you need to be afraid of.
[Valentina coughs]
[device clicks]
[sighs]
Good girl.
You came to your senses.
Come here. Help me up.
- I want a raise.
- Hmm.
- [elevator bell dings]
- [Valentina] Okay, fine.
Get cleanup on the body.
And tell Holt
it's finally time
to go lethal on these losers.
[Alexei] Yelena!
- Little one.
- Go away.
No, I will not.
Well, then, chase me forever.
Fine, I will, because
that's what family does.
Oh, my God, stop.
If you cared,
you would have called.
I would have heard from you.
I lost my sister again,
but forever.
And you disappeared.
[Alexei speaks Russian]
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to do this.
I'm not good at it.
I didn't think you wanted me.
I did.
I see that.
I'm late, but I'm...
I'm here now.
Daddy, I'm so alone.
I don't have anything anymore.
All I do is sit
and look at my phone
and think of all the terrible
things that I've done.
And then I go to work.
And then I drink.
And then I come home
to no one.
And I sit
and I think about all
the terrible things I've done
- again and again.
- Yelena, stop. Stop.
And I go crazy.
We all have things
that we regret.
No, but I have so many.
My first test at the Red Room.
Anya. She was just a child.
- She was so small.
- So were you.
I Know.
I know there were dark times.
Very, very dark times.
But before, you were such
a special little girl.
Did you know this?
You walked into a room.
You made it brighter.
You felt a lot of joy.
I don't remember that feeling.
You were so kind.
Do you remember why
you want to be goalie
on your terrible soccer team?
I...
So I didn't have
to run as much.
[chuckling] No.
Maybe that too,
but you told me,
"I want to be the one
everyone can rely on
if they make a mistake."
That Lena is still in you.
I still see her.
I don't.
You're stuck. You're alone.
You look only at the bad.
When I look at you,
I don't see your mistakes.
That's why we need each other.
Okay, that was really good.
[people chattering]
- Val?
- Yeah?
It's cleanup
from the penthouse,
and they're saying, well,
there's no body.
What?
[gasps]
[agent] I don't know
what I'm looking at up here.
It doesn't look good.
Aren't you tired of fighting?
Let me help you.
Holt, are you seeing this?
Is that...
Oh, no.
[people clamoring]
It's time.
[rumbling]
Follow me!
Go, go! Go!
[horn blares]
Dad!
Come on. You've got to...
You've got to--
[screaming]
[civilian screaming]
[all straining]
[all panting]
[crowd applauding, cheering]
[child] Mom?
[rumbling]
You're safe, little one.
[crowd screaming, clamoring]
You all know the truth.
You can't outrun
the emptiness.
I think Bob's dark side
got superpowers.
- Get everybody off the street.
- Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Everybody! Come on! Come on!
- Go, go, go!
- Go, go! Inside, inside!
[Alexei] Go, everyone, inside!
Let's go! Get in. Get in.
Yelena!
- [Bucky] Come on.
- [Walker] Go, go, go!
Yelena, what are you doing?
It's what you said.
We're all alone.
All of us.
[Alexei] Wait!
Yelena!
- No, no, no! No! No, no!
- [Ava] Hey, hey, hey. Come on.
[cries]
Yelena!
[in Russian] Yelena, c'mon!
[in Russian]
Lunch will be over soon.
Why'd you bring us so far out?
[in Russian] Anya, over here!
[in Russian] I'm sorry.
Bob!
[gunshot]
Yelena!
[speaking Russian]
- No. No.
- [young Yelena speaks Russian]
No, no, no!
No! No, no, no! No!
[in Russian]
It's too late for that, friend.
[grunting]
[Anya] Yelena!
[speaking Russian]
Bob!
[Anya speaking Russian]
[straining]
[speaks Russian]
[gunshot]
[teacher speaking Russian]
Bob! We don't
have time for this.
Stop.
[speaking Russian]
[teacher speaking Russian]
There you are.
[both grunting]
[Alexei crying]
- I'm going after her.
- And then what?
If she did that,
she did it for a reason.
Well, what if she's dead, huh?
What if there's
no coming back?
What if she isn't?
How do you know that?
No, no, no, wait, hold on.
I think she might
have a point.
When-- When I was back in
the vault, |-I saw something.
I-I went somewhere.
I can't explain it, but...
What did you see?
Enough, Bob.
Enough.
[Bob] Yelena?
Hi.
Hey.
I just want to talk, okay?
About what?
About the stuff we spoke about
in the vault.
Hi.
What's up?
Um...
Not much. You know, just
watching New York disappear
into a big maze
of interconnected shame rooms.
You ever seen anything crazy
like that before?
I-- I don't know
what you want me to say.
That you'll stop.
Oh, it's not "me" me.
It's-- It's-- It's it.
The Void.
I-- I have these good days,
you know?
Where I feel...
I feel invincible.
But then there are
a lot of bad days
when I remember
that nothing...
nothing matters, you know?
So you're just gonna sit here
and let it take over?
Well, there's no use
in fighting it.
At least I found a nice room.
The other rooms
are much worse.
It is nice
and quiet here, yeah.
- [Bob's father] What was that?
- [glass smashes]
- Disrespected in my own house!
- [smack]
- [Bob's mother groans]
- Don't mind them.
- It'll be over soon.
- [smack]
[Bob's father] Say it again!
Say it again, Annie!
[Annie] I-- I shouldn't have.
I'm sorry.
[young Bob] Don't touch her.
[Bob's father]
Big man speaks up.
- Bob, shut your mouth.
- Mom, no.
My son, the hero. Look at you.
- What are you gonna do?
- Bob. Sit down.
You a hero, Bobby?
[Annie] Sit down.
You're making it worse.
You always made it worse.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
[sniffling]
What I said to you before
was wrong, Bob.
You can't stuff it down.
You can't hold it in
all alone.
No one can.
We have to let it out.
We have
to spend time together.
And even if it doesn't
make the emptiness go away,
I promise you
it will feel lighter.
How do you know?
[rumbling]
Because it already has for me.
[rumbling fades]
We can find a way out
of here together.
Will you try and leave here
with me?
[rumbling resumes]
Okay.
Look out!
[grunts]
Who's doing this, Bob?
I think I am.
Just try to get
used to it, okay?
There's no death here.
The pain only gets worse.
[groans, shouts]
Evil pillow!
[sighs]
Lena.
[panting]
You came for us.
What did you see?
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
I have a great past,
so I'm totally fine.
Yeah, this place is messed up.
We're here together.
That's what matters.
Thank you, guys. Really.
Of course.
Here we are, Shane's Elite
Electronic Thunderbolts.
It's not Shane.
Okay, okay. Just how-how
do we get out of here?
I mean, as-- as far as I know,
it's just endless rooms.
Wait, you said that this was
the nicest room you found
and the others
are way worse, right?
Yeah.
Okay, well, show us the worst.
Where do you think
you're going, Robert?
[grunts]
[Ava] Well, he seems nice.
The strangest mission
I've ever been part of.
- This way!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on. Come on.
[laughs, clucks]
Oh, no.
Bob, you hit me with
that sign one more time--
[groans]
I was on meth!
[shouts]
This way!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
I've been here before.
This is where it started.
I was roaming
around Southeast Asia,
thought I'd figure
something out,
or at least find more drugs.
Then there was this guy,
started talking to me
about a-- a medical study.
A trial drug that could
make me stronger.
Felt like a miracle.
I'd finally get to show
everyone that I was more.
That I was...
something.
And look what you unleashed.
The most shameful thing
of all was
thinking you could be
anything more than
nothing.
We're leaving.
No.
[both groan]
[groans]
[group groaning]
Stop.
Just... let-- let them go.
Wait. You think they care
about you?
You don't matter.
To anyone.
That's not true.
[groans]
[Alexei] No!
Don't hurt her.
Robert, the hero.
[Yelena grunts]
I'm stronger than you.
Let's see.
[grunting]
Get up, Bobby.
You thought you were
gonna be some great man?
Some savior?
You can't even save yourself.
We will always be alone.
Is that all you've got?
[Void laughs, groans]
[Bob] No.
[laughing continues]
[Yelena groans, gasps]
This isn't right.
Bob, stop!
This is what he wants!
[Alexei strains]
I'm here.
It will always be just us.
I'm here. You are not alone.
Come on.
[all grunt]
[mother] Sweetie.
You were great in there, Bob.
[chuckles]
Thanks, Walker.
[stammering]
Hey, wait, in where?
Whoa.
What happened here?
Sorry, I'm-- I'm just
a little-- I'm a little fuzzy.
[Alexei laughs]
Okay. Are you serious?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[Valentina] Yes. I need
an extraction right now.
What? No. I don't have backup.
I need help.
I'm going to kill that person.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
What happens when
he regains his memory?
- Okay. Come on.
- Oh, me too?
Yep. We stick together
from now on.
That's nice.
Can't kill her.
We gotta take her in.
Maybe when we take her in,
I break a few bones.
Oh, I'd like to Kill her.
Maybe when he does
get his memory back,
he can fix this stupid thing.
At least let me
break her legs.
- Okay, guys.
- Then you can drag her.
I know we're all having
a lot of feelings right now.
- I am too. I get it.
- Hi.
Give me half-- half a second.
[reporters clamoring]
Are we live?
Great.
For years, I have been
working secretly
to develop a new age
of protection.
Today, the citizens
of the United States needed
that protection.
And thanks to my hard work,
they got it.
Ladies and gentlemen...
meet...
the new Avengers.
[reporters clamoring]
We own you now.
[whistles]
Wow, so many choices, huh?
Hard to decide.
Oh, look, Wheaties. Wow.
With its toasted
wholewheat flakes,
wholegrain, vitamins.
Give you energy.
Good for kids, huh?
[chuckles] Okay.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
That's me on the box.
[♪ Starship
"Nothing's Gonna Stop Us Now"]
♪ And we can
Build this dream together ♪
♪ Standing strong forever ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna
Stop us now ♪
♪ And if this world
Runs out of lovers ♪
♪ We'll still have
Each other ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna stop us ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ All that I need is you ♪
♪ All that I ever need ♪
♪ And all that I want to do ♪
♪ ls hold you forever ♪
♪ Forever and ever ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ And we can build
This dream together >♪
♪ Standing strong forever ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna
Stop us now ♪
♪ And if this world
Runs out of lovers ♪
♪ We'll still have
Each other ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna stop us ♪
- ♪ Nothing's gonna stop us ♪
- ♪ And we can ♪
♪ Build this dream together
Standing strong forever ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna
Stop us now ♪
[song fades]
[Yelena]
But we are the Avengers.
The government said so.
How does Sam Wilson
not understand that?
[Bucky] Well, he does have the shield.
- Well, I got a shield too.
- It's not a shield.
- Yeah, it is a shield.
- It's a shitty shield.
It's a great shield, Bucky.
Okay,
if he puts together a team,
and then the team is
called the Avengers,
who are the real Avengers?
[Walker] That's the question
the Internet has been asking,
and judging by the very nasty
memes that I've read,
they don't think that it's us.
Weren't you going
to talk to him?
I already did.
- And?
- It went poorly.
I don't know
what any of these buttons do.
It's unbelievable
they didn't mark any of them.
You know he's filed
for copyright of the name?
- Did he?
- We're losing credibility.
Which we had very little
to begin with.
And now there's this huge
space crisis,
and no one's telling us
about it.
We're running out of space?
It's impossible.
This building is enormous.
- What?
- Outer space.
Outer space.
Run a threat analysis.
I want a full report.
[computer]
Running threat analysis.
Hello, team.
[Bucky]
The hell are you wearing?
I heard about Sam Wilson.
He's dumb, litigious man,
but I am smart.
I am smart man.
I have smart solve.
Avengerz.
With a 'Z, '
there is no copyright.
- No.
- So soft too.
Feel like bottom of baby seal.
You want to...
you want to savor that?
I don't want to touch
your baby seal butt.
- Have one for you.
- I don't want it.
I have one for you.
I got you one.
And for you, Bob,
in the corner hiding,
pretending to read the book.
We're all matching.
All part of super team!
[alarm beeping]
[computer] Unidentified craft
entering orbit.
You should get
a satellite image.
- Uh. Get a satellite image.
- And fire up--
And fire... I was gonna say
that. And fire up the jets.
We wouldn't need
to fire up the jets
if we had a Sentry
who could fly.
I know... Sorry. Sorry, guys.
Can't be the Sentry without
the, you know, other side.
I did the dishes though.
And what are we gonna do,
just ride Bob into the sky?
Yes.
Can you imagine Red Guardian
riding on top of Sentry,
cresting over the clouds?
This is why we are Avengers
with a 'Z.'
[computer]
Satellite image populating.
Extradimensional ship
entering atmosphere.
[Alexei] Extradimensional?
What does that mean?
[Walker] It's a...
it's a cool ship.